<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Olaya</string>
    <string name="Olaya">Olaya is a municipality of Colombia, located in the West Subregion of the Department of Antioquia. It limits north with the municipality of Liborina, east with the municipalities of Belmira and Sopetran, by the south with the municipality of Sopetran and the west with the municipality of Santa Fe de Antioquia. Its municipal header is 100 km from Medellín. It has an extension of 90 km², which makes it the smallest municipality of the subregion, below Giraldo and Armenia, 96 km² and 111 km², respectively. In addition to a Colombian town.
     The municipality has as appellative "laya magic land of sunsets and mountains",. Given that it is located in a region of sum historical activity, Olaya is considered one of the oldest municipalities in the department.</string>
    <string name="Bandejapaisa">Well known for all the Antioquenos and Olaya do not stay behind a dish that is served in restaurants in the municipality and festivities such as the day of antiolation, it is also very common to see this dish in homes at lunchtime.</string>
    <string name="Quebrada">One of the main actracters that you should visit if you arrive in the municipality with its waterfall that throws abundant water, surrounded by diversity of fauna and flora, and with its incredible wonderful history to everyone who visits it, since it is said that indigenous ethnicity inhabited this Place in past times.</string>
    <string name="Iglesia">The Church is also a very attractive place to visit is one of the oldest in the municipality, this dazzles in the opted times, since it is one of the few that has a mobile manger installed in the inside of this. </string>
    <string name="Fiestasdelverano">These holidays are celebrated the first days of January a great tradition that has generations in the municipality of people from different parties come to enjoy these, in this weekend of partying takes place a reign where different municipalities of the area are invited to participate, And also a set of orchestras that people enjoy.</string>
    <string name="virgen">The parties are celebrated in the month of August in honor of the virgin of Nieves Patrona del Municipality, counts the legend that some time tried to steal the statue of the Virgin, and half the road became so heavy that they could not take the robbery .</string>
    <string name="opcion1">About us</string>
    <string name="opcion2">English</string>
    <string name="opcion3">Spanish</string>
    <string name="descripcion">My name is Juan Pablo Hinestroza Ospina I am 18 years old. I am a student of the CESDE studying the penulty semester,
         of development of Sotfware, I work as a practitioner in EOUNO Consulting, my favorite hobby is playing football my favorite team is a national athletic,
         My dream is to be a great developer and fulfill all my proposed goals.
    </string>
</resources>